Hello friends welcome back to my channel
ICICI Lombard does health
insurance work and it is doing
remote jobs for insurance agents so
let me tell you about the
work of health insurance so
if you
are an agent of any esteem company or a life insurance agent of any esteem company
or want to do insurance work of any esteem company then
despite that you can do health insurance work of any other company
so if you are from
LIC or HDFC then also
you can apply here in ICICI Lombard that
means
we can do health insurance of any company for you so
if you are
qualified then there is no problem at all if you are
not then they have
not given the details of the case
it makes you qualify the IRDA exam
and it charges some fees for it so when you
apply in it then in the return it will be
told to you that you will have to qualify this exam and
this fee will be charged for it so
apart from this if you have any queries or you want to
ask anything then here  The recruiter's note number
is given here, Rahul Chaudhary, okay, you
can talk to him by sending a message here,
apart from this, he has also given his WhatsApp number,
okay, so this is
88956 3377, through this you can talk directly through
WhatsApp or by calling,
okay,
you can clear all your queries, okay, here is
its apply link and along with this,
one more benefit is being provided to you,
medical insurance, okay, you are seeing the
benefits found in your post, then this
medical is provided to all the
employees there, okay, so
I will give you its apply link in the description,
if you like my channel, then
subscribe to it because I keep
providing such latest job updates,
thank you